

Profile

Web developer with 10 years of experience developing and supporting websites for digital agencies, universities and governmental entities. As a backend developer she has programming web projects on MVC(Model-View-Controller) architecture with Laravel framework, custom made projects based on PHP Stack and supporting CMS websites in Drupal and Wordpress. As a frontend developer she has got skills making UI templates, landing pages, forms, SPA(Single Page Apps) and APIs consumption. In addition to the above, she is able to follow and deal with the client requirements getting a useful and friendly digital product.

Employment History

Full Stack web developer at Geometry Global Colombia, Bogotá, Colombia

june 2019 - may 2021

Had experience building and supporting websites projects for digital marketing strategies based on PHP Stack. Skilled developing projects based on Laravel framework. Had experience supporting CMS websites in Drupal and Wordpress as a frontend. Capable of integrating payment gateways and 3rd party APIs consumption.

Frontend web developer at Bogotá City Hall, Bogotá, Colombia

july 2018 - december 2019

Was responsible for making frontend layouting for components, views and blocks in Drupal 8 CMS based on Bootstrap CSS, Javascript, jQuery, and SASS.

PHP SSr Developer en Seidor Colombia, Bogotá, Colombia

january 2016 - january 2017

Developed and supported a Ministry of Telecommunications (MINTIC) solution based in PHP stack over 2600 websites about governmental entities.

Education

System Engineering Bachelor Degree, Universidad Simón Bolívar, Cúcuta, Colombia

february 2000 - march 2006

Multimedia Management Postgraduate Program, Universidad Santo Tomás

may 2013 - april 2015

Frontend Nanodegree Program, Udacity AT&T Aspire to Tech Scholarship Program

june 2017 - january 2018

Details

Bogotá, D.C. Colombia (+57) 313 355 1203 claudiaeforero@hotmail.com

Links

<u>LinkedIn</u> <u>Web Portfolio</u> GitHub

Technical Skills

HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Bootstrap 4, Javascript, jQuery, ReactJS + Redux, VueJS. PHP, Laravel, Drupal, Wordpress. Python. MySQL, GIT, Postman.

Hard Skills

POO, MVC, SPA, APIs consumption, user experience, accessibility, site content structure, SEO, web performance. Payment gateway integrations.

Soft Skills

Analytical, creative, recursive, aesthetic, logical, focused on details, quality, sensitive.

Languages

Spanish(Native), English (Intermediate B2), French(Basic)